
const trivia = [
  { // 1
    question: "Was the original iPhone released before this day in 2007?",
    answer: 1 // yes
  },
  { // 2
    question: "Was the Netflix streaming service launched before this day in 2007?",
    answer: 1 // yes
  },
  { // 3
    question: "Was the original Amazon Kindle released before this day in 2007?",
    answer: 2 // no
  },
  { // 4
    question: "Was Google Street View released before this day in 2007?",
    answer: 1 // yes
  },
  { // 5
    question: "Was Spongebob started before this day in 2007?",
    answer: 2 // no
  },
  { // 6
    question: "Did Johnny Test air before this day in 2007?",
    answer: 1 // yes
  },
  { // 7
    question: "Was the Phineas and Ferb pilot released before this day in 2007?",
    answer: 1 // yes
  },
  { // 8
    question: "Did Adventure Time air before this day in 2007?",
    answer: 2 // no
  },
  { // 9
    question: "Did the Penguins of Madagascar air before this day in 2007?",
    answer: 2 // no
  },
  { // 10
    question: "Did Avatar: the Last Airbender air before this day in 2007?",
    answer: 1 // yes 
  }
];
